Aisance BIKOKA

Full Stack developer

Profil

I am interested in user-centered design, UX/UI design, application prototyping (Figma, Adobe Xd), and software development, both on the backend (Java, Python, Node.js, SQL databases, etc.) and the web frontend (Angular, React.js, HTML, CSS.). My diverse experience on various academic, personal, and entreprise projects enables me to be versatile and independent in the execution of my projects, from gathering requirements to delivery.

Contact



0605937118



aisanceb@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/aisance-bikoka-30266a254



7 Avenue Edouard Belin 31400

Soft Skills

- Team work
- Critical thinking
- Effective communication
- Leadership

Languages

- French (Fluent)
- English (Intermediate)

Hobbies

- Music (Singer)
- Volleyball (Attacker and Libero)
- Soccer (GoalKeeper and defender)

Work experience

Air France-KLM | Valbonne-Sophia Antipolis 04/2024- Present

Design and Implementation of the CGOCCL application interface for Cargo activities to follow customs declarations.

Technologies used:

- Figma
- Angular, TypeScript, HTML, Tailwind, Scss
- Java Spring Boot.

Fans4All et SII (group project) | Toulouse 09/2023-03/2024

Design and Implementation of two interfaces for the exchange of traffic information between an air traffic controller and HSI (Hearing and Speaking Impaired) pilote.

Technologies used:

- Figma
- React Native.

University of York | York, United Kingdom's 06/2023-08/2024

Trainee in HCI homeLab on Attitude of elderly people on social robots

- Preparation and configuration of robots for workshops, presentation of robots to elderly people one by one.
- Completion of a questionnaire for an evaluation of the robots' ability to provide assistance to elderly people, taking notes of the real and critical needs of elderly people in relation to robots to publish an article.

Education

Double degree ENAC / Paul SABATIER university 2023-2024

- IT system of Air Transport Engineer
- Master's degree in Human Computer Interaction (HCI)